http://www.spinergy.com/privacy-policy

Shopping Cart
Total: $0.00
Total: $0.00
You must have Javascript enabled to use this form.
Log in
You must have Javascript enabled to use this form.
Log In
Your shopping cart is empty.
Home
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy applies to Spinergy’s website located at www.spinergy.com (the "Website"). The purpose of this privacy policy is to disclose to you what information we may collect, how we may collect it, with whom we may share it, and certain other matters related to such information, including the choices you have regarding our collection of information and our use and disclosure to other parties of information we may have collected from you.
When this privacy policy uses the term "personally identifiable information"; or "personal information,"; we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as your full name, street address or email address. When other information, such as personal security questions is associated with personal information, it also becomes personally identifiable information for the purposes of this privacy policy.
Please read the information below to learn more about our data collection policies and practices.
Types Of Information That May Be Collected
How Information May Be Collected
How We Use The Information Collected
With Whom The Information May Be Shared
Security
Chat Rooms, Forums, And Message Boards
Links To Other Websites
A Special Note For Parents Concerning Privacy
Notification Of Changes And Your Acceptance Of The Privacy Policy
Correcting/Updating Personal Information
Your California Privacy Rights
Questions About This Privacy Policy
TYPES OF INFORMATION THAT MAY BE COLLECTED
The following are the types of information we may collect:
Information You Provide Us: In the course of using the website, we may ask you to provide us with certain information, including contact information, such as your name, mailing address, and email address; unique identifiers, such as your user id and password; and other information such as date of birth, gender or nationality for example.
Site Usage Information: We may receive and store certain types of internet usage information whenever you visit the Website, such as your IP Address and click stream data. See "IP Addresses and Click Stream Data"; section below.
Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you.
HOW INFORMATION MAY BE COLLECTED
We may collect information from you in several different areas on the Website, including but not limited to those described below:
Registration: You may be asked to complete a registration form and provide personally identifiable information; you may also be asked to choose a user ID and password in order to take advantage of certain features the Website may choose to offer, such as to request tickets to upcoming events, access your profile, receive news updates and to use the site forums. Participation in registration is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.
Newsletters and Website Emails: We offer free newsletters to share information with you about the Website, about us and our affiliates and subsidiaries, or about our marketing partners and advertisers and sponsors. You may receive a newsletter either by registering for a particular newsletter or in conjunction with a special feature or membership for which you have registered on the Website. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. You may also cancel your free email subscription by following the instructions provided on the Website or in the newsletter or email.
Tell-A-Friend: If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. The Website does not store this information as its sole purpose is to send this as a one-time email.
Contests or Sweepstakes: We periodically operate contests and sweepstakes through the Website that may require registration or the submission of personal information. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website. Your personally identifiable information may be used to contact you for winner notification, prize delivery confirmation or other related purposes, (see the rules of each contest for details about how your personal information will be used). We may also ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the Website, such as on a winner's page, in the event you win a contest or sweepstakes. Except as required by applicable law, we will not post your information without your permission. In some instances, a third party advertiser or sponsor may operate or host a contest or sweepstakes on the Website, and collect your information. In those cases, where we are not the operator or host of the contest or sweepstakes, we do not collect your information and we have no control over the information collected from you. Accordingly, we urge you to review the advertiser's or sponsor's privacy policy applicable to the contest or sweepstakes before participating.
Surveys or Voting: From time-to-time we may request personally identifiable information from you in conjunction with a survey or voting poll. Participation is voluntary and you will have the opportunity to decide whether or not to disclose information to the Website.
Cookies: As with many Websites, our Website uses a technology called "cookies." A cookie is a unique, random number that is stored in the browser on your computer. The cookie doesn't actually identify you, just the computer that is used to visit the site. Cookies automatically identify your browser to the Website whenever your computer is used to visit the Website. Cookies also let us know how many people visit our website and where visitors go on the site. In addition, cookies can let us know non-personally identifiable information, like what web browser is being used to access the website. For registered users, cookies can make using the Website easier for you by saving information such as your passwords or preferences. By tracking how and when you use the Website, cookies help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the Website are based on data obtained from cookies. Accepting cookies allows you, among other things, to personalize your experience on the Website. Cookies may also allow the Website to present to you advertising which may be of interest to you. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, your browser should contain an option that allows you to disable or delete cookie data at any time. Some areas of the Website, however, may not provide you with a personalized experience if you have disabled the use of cookies.
We may allow third party tracking services to place cookies on our website to track aggregate statistics as mentioned above. These cookies do not track any personally identifiable information about visitors or members to the website.
IP Addresses and Click-Stream Data: We may collect IP addresses and/or click-stream data. An IP address is a number associated with the service through which you access the Internet, like your ISP (Internet service provider), your company, or your university. Standing alone, your IP address is not personally identifiable. At times, we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our sites. We may combine this information with personally identifiable information. Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request Web pages from the Website. Click-stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed, this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the Website, what type of content is most popular, what type of visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.
Transaction Information: We currently do not collect any financial information from our users. If you make a purchase through the Spinergy store, please be aware that you are providing any and all personal information directly to Spinergy. .
HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED
As applicable, the information you provide to us may be used to:
contact you about the Website;
contact you relating to your membership status, or in response to your request for more information;
confirm or fulfill an order you have made;
inform you of a prize you have won;
monitor or improve the use of the Website;
customize the advertising and content you see;
monitor compliance with our terms and conditions of use of the Website; and
send you promotional material or special offers on behalf of our marketing partners and/or their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties.
WITH WHOM THE INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED
At times, we may share with or have a third party directly collect your personal information for various purposes. The following outlines the ways in which this may occur in relation to activities on our site and the ways in which you may opt-out of having your information shared:
Agents: We employ other businesses, certain services and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include Website analysis, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, Website hosting and design, and providing customer service. They may have access to personally identifiable information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for their own purposes, like sending you marketing offers about their products.
In some instances, you may be linked to an outside Web site where the pages may display the Spinergy branding or look and feel of the Spinergy Web site. Please note that you are submitting your information directly to these third party sites even though these pages have the look and feel of our site. It will be clear on these pages the entity collecting your personal information and you should refer to the privacy statement available from these pages.
Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographics and Website usage statistics, with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations. When this type of information is shared, the other parties do not have access to your personally identifiable information.
Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We do not share personal information with any third parties for marketing purposes.
Third-Party Ad Serving & Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: The Website may use a third party network advertiser to serve the advertisements on the Website or may use a traffic measurement service to analyze the traffic on the Website. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements based on your visits to this Website and other Websites you have visited. Third-party ad serving enables us to target advertisements to you for products or Websites you might be interested in. Audience and Traffic Measurement Services allow us to collect anonymous traffic and behavior information from our Website by monitoring anonymous visitor activity. Although advertisers or other companies do not have access to the Website cookies, the Website's advertisers, sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies on your computer if you choose to have your cookies enabled in your browser. Cookies allow third party advertisers to show you advertisements or content you might be interested in. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.
Business Transfers: In the event that all or substantially all of our assets are sold or transferred to another party, or another transaction occurs in which your personally identifiable information is one of the business assets transferred, all personally identifiable information that has been collected and saved may be one of the business assets we transfer. See "Your Acceptance of the Privacy Policy and Notification of Changes to the Policy"; section below.
Administrative or Legal Process: Your personal information may be transferred to third parties without notice to you in order to comply with applicable law, law enforcement agencies, to protect our rights, or protect the rights of other users of this website.
CHAT ROOMS, FORUMS, AND MESSAGE BOARDS
The Website may make chat rooms, forums and message boards available to its users. You are not required to provide any personal information when using these areas but you may choose to do so. If you post personal information online, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties. We cannot ensure the security of any information you choose to make public in a chat room, forum, or message board. Also, we cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy. Please exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these areas.
LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES
You should be aware that when you are on the Website you could be directed to other Websites beyond our control. For example, if you "click" on a banner advertisement, the "click" may take you off the Website onto a different Website. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors and marketing partners that may use the Website's logo as part of a co-branding agreement. These other Websites may send their own cookies to you, independently collect data or solicit personal information and may or may not have their own published privacy policies. If you visit a Website that is linked to our Website, you should consult that Website's privacy policy before providing any personal information.
SECURITY
This Website incorporates reasonable safeguards to protect the security, integrity, completeness, accuracy and privacy of the personal information that we may collect and we have put into place reasonable precautions to protect such information from loss, misuse and alteration. Your personally identifiable information is transferred to our computers utilizing encryption software. Only those employees who need access to your information in order to do their jobs are allowed access. Our security policies are reviewed periodically and revised as required.
A SPECIAL NOTE FOR PARENTS CONCERNING PRIVACY
The Website is a general audience Website. We do not currently collect any personal information directly from children under the age of thirteen on the Website.
The Internet offers children wonderful educational and entertainment resources. Your guidance and involvement are essential to help ensure that children have a safe and rewarding online experience. We encourage you to visit the Direct Marketing Association's Web Website (www.the-dma.org) and explore the Get CyberSavvy! Program as well as the GetNetWise Website (www.getnetwise.org)to learn more about parental control tools.
YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THE PRIVACY POLICY AND NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO THE POLICY
By using this Website, you signify your agreement to the terms of our privacy policy. We may amend this privacy policy at any time. If we make a material change to the way in which we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will post a notice on our website and / or send an email to users who have provided an email address. We will assume that you have given your permission for your information to be used under the terms of the new privacy policy, if you do not respond to our email within thirty days or continue to use the Website thirty days after a notice is posted. Please note that you should always update your personal information to provide us with a current email address.
CORRECTING/UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION
If your personally identifiable information changes (such as your email address or zip code), or if you no longer desire to access our Website, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove the personal data you have provided to us.
For information collected during registration, you may access your collected information by logging into your account and changing your information.
You may also Contact Us regarding information collected in other areas of our Web site.
QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY
If you have any questions about this privacy policy or the privacy practices of this Website, Contact Us
Questions regarding this statement should be directed to:
Spinergy Inc.,
1914 Palomar Oaks Way, Suite 100
Carlsbad, CA 92008
